Real War, Real Heroes
The Hornet's Nest is a war, documentary, history
film directed by David Salzberg.
Armed only with their cameras, Peabody and Emmy Award-winning conflict Journalist Mike Boettcher,
and his son, Carlos, provide unprecedented access into the longest war in U.S.
history: they are embed with U.S.
troops during nine days of intense combat in Afghanistan.
Himself, played by Carlos Boettcher.
Himself, played by Mike Boettcher.
Himself, played by Kalen M. Waite.
The Hornet's Nest is a 2014 American documentary film about the Afghanistan war,
directed and produced by David Salzberg and Christian Tureaud.
The film follows father and son journalists Mike Boettcher and Carlos Boettcher, embedded with a group of United States Army soldiers from
101st Airborne Division sent on a mission into Kunar Province's Barawala Kalay Valley, one of Afghanistan's most hostile valleys.
The three-day mission becomes an intense nine
days of fighting against the enemy.
The film explores themes of explosive, afghanistan, afghanistan war (2001-2021).
The tone is intense.